Here's the message we received.
This is a request we received from a radio name Kakan-kun
Please tell us a wonderful story about Haruna Sakamoto.
Okay, we'll answer your request and bring you the best story of all!
The kettle and the idol
I didn't get a definite OK.
Give me a look.
Cut it off? Like...
Cut it out.
I've been watching you.
The same kind of woman from the sea.
What's with that woman?
She goes to the beach and drives a water bike
They're barbecuing on the beach
There are quite a lot of songs
I haven't said this very often.
This might be a first.
It might be the first time.
I got some good stuff out of him.
I was a kettle, but I did my best.
Kettle and idols
Hello, I'm Mr. Night, from Starcraft's middle class upbringing.
I'd like to introduce today's guest, an idol.
I'm Haruna Sakamoto from Team Shachi.
I'm Haruna Sakamoto from Team Shachi, nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
As for Team Shachi, I'm sure all three of you have already appeared on the show.
The last one, Mr. Sakamoto, is the MC of a radio show in his hometown, Nagoya, called Oshimashi.
So it's starting in October 2019?
Yes, Oshimashi itself will start in 2019, and before that, Nagaoka Scramble was on every Thursday night from 10pm in the same time slot.
That was in the same time slot every Thursday night from 10:00 p.m. If you do the calculations, it started in 2017.
I don't know how long it's been, but it's been 6 years.
It's been 6 years!
I'm usually the idol who appears on the show, but I'm not the one who welcomes the guests.
But in the show, I'm the one who welcomes the guests, aren't I?You are the one who welcomes the guests on the show.
What do you keep in mind as the MC of the show?
As the MC of the show?
Yes, I am.
Wow.
But it's precisely because I've experienced being on the show as well.
I've also had the experience of being on the show, so I'm thinking about what I'd be happy to hear if I were on the show when I release a new album.
I'm also aware of what fans would be happy to hear.
I also keep in mind what fans would be happy to hear.
That's a comment from a middle school student.
Thank you very much.
By the way, what has been the most exciting thing about being in charge of this program?
Well, there are so many, but we are very close as a team.
We've celebrated each other's birthdays with lots of surprises.
But we also get a lot of messages from listeners asking for advice.
At one point, we started getting a lot of love advice from our listeners.
I talked about it with Sakai-kun, who works with me, and he gave me some advice.
He gave me some advice on what I should do, and we came up with a version that was successful.
There is also a pattern where the person was rejected because of that.
I'm probably happiest when people tell me about their experiences.
Do you have listeners who come to the award show and give you answers to the e-mails you sent them?
Yes, I do.
Yes?
There are a lot of award shows during the release event season.
When listeners come wearing goods made of oshimashi, it makes me feel that they are my listeners.
When I think that they are my listeners, I can't really see their expressions on their faces or anything like that on the radio, just their voices.
I feel like I'm speaking more frankly because I'm speaking in a casual way.
I feel like I'm talking to them as if I'm their friend because I'm talking to them in a casual way.
I feel like they're my friends.
I feel at ease when all the listeners are there.
That's something new and exciting.
It makes me happy.
Being able to see their faces and hear their voices is a little different from the usual radio show.
Yes, it's different.
That's why I'm hoping that you'll see me live in the spring and tell me you like me.That's why if you see Spring at a live show and tell me you like it.
It's like they like almost everything.
I get the feeling that he's even more intense.
What? When did you go to Spring?
I have a big show coming up.
You've got a lot of rehearsals and stuff.
And this show...
Mr. Pusshinaburi no Mono
Kokoro-san
Black Dog
Zenichi
Mr. Shito Torora
Thank you very much!
It's going to be a hot day, so eat shaved ice to cool off!